What are you messing with behind those screens?
ما الذي تعبث به خلف تلك الشاشات؟
It is useless.
إنه عديم الفائدة.
Looks like some little rats
يبدو أنها بعض الفئران الصغيرة
are secretly watching us.
إنهم يراقبوننا سراً.
[Affinity]
[التقارب]
I think I accidentally pressed the elevator intercom.
أعتقد أنني ضغطت على جهاز الاتصال الداخلي للمصعد عن طريق الخطأ.
They're coming.
إنهم قادمون.
Metal detector.
جهاز كشف المعادن.
Found it.
وجدته.
Is it this one?
هل هو هذا؟
Yes.
نعم.
That's it.
هذا كل شيء.
There's no time.
ليس هناك وقت.
Throw it to me.
ألقِها إليّ.
We still have time.
لا يزال لدينا وقت.
[Out of Service]
[خارج الخدمة]
Your stamina is terrible.
قدرتك على التحمل سيئة للغاية.
But you think fast.
لكنك تفكر بسرعة.
I'm getting old.
أنا أتقدم في السن.
Give me a hand.
ساعدني.
The elevator won't hold much longer.
لن يصمد المصعد لفترة أطول.
We need to split up.
علينا أن ننفصل.
I'll go up and tell everyone to evacuate.
سأصعد وأطلب من الجميع الإخلاء.
You head to the satellite signal station.
تتجه إلى محطة إشارات الأقمار الصناعية.
That's a satellite signal.
هذه إشارة قمر صناعي.
They can't cut it.
لا يمكنهم فعل ذلك.
Let her go with you.
دعها تذهب معك.
It's hard for me to take someone along.
من الصعب عليّ اصطحاب شخص ما معي.
All right, Nongyu.
حسناً، نونغيو.
You come with me.
ستأتي معي.
By the way,
بالمناسبة،
the elevator is dangerous.
المصعد خطير.
Take the stairs.
اصعد الدرج.
Fifty-four floors is brutal.
أربعة وخمسون طابقاً أمرٌ قاسٍ.
But try
لكن حاول
to finish within thirty minutes.
لإنجاز المهمة في غضون ثلاثين دقيقة.
Fifty four floors?
أربعة وخمسون طابقاً؟
That's terrifying.
هذا أمر مرعب.
Mr. Gu.
السيد غو.
I'll go to the signal station with you.
سأذهب معك إلى محطة الإشارة.
I promise I won't slow you down.
أعدك أنني لن أؤخرك.
Hey.
يا.
Is that building next to us newly built?
هل المبنى المجاور لنا حديث البناء؟
Yes.
نعم.
The new transit station is there too.
محطة النقل الجديدة موجودة هناك أيضاً.
It's scheduled to open next month.
من المقرر افتتاحه الشهر المقبل.
Then we can use that transit route to get out.
ثم يمكننا استخدام طريق النقل هذا للخروج.
What about
ماذا عن
we crack this code first.
نحن نفك هذا الرمز أولاً.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Sorry.
آسف.
I was just checking
كنت أتحقق فقط
for any clues inside.
للحصول على أي أدلة بالداخل.
I did not expect that
لم أتوقع ذلك
everything would fall out.
كل شيء سينهار.
So it is not a keypad.
إذن فهي ليست لوحة مفاتيح.
It is a fax machine.
إنها آلة فاكس.
The Special Administration Bureau
مكتب الإدارة الخاصة
is 0409.
هو 0409.
[Sending]
[إرسال]
Must be a tripped circuit.
لا بد أن الدائرة الكهربائية قد تعطلت.
I'll check the electrical room in the stairwell.
سأفحص غرفة الكهرباء في درج المبنى.
Call out if anything happens.
أبلغ عن أي شيء يحدث.
[Sending]
[إرسال]
[Sent]
[مرسل]
Is Mr. Gu stuck?
هل السيد غو عالق؟
A Ren.
رين.
Run.
يجري.
Up here.
هنا في الأعلى.
Hold tight.
تمسك جيداً.
They should not be able to catch up.
لا ينبغي أن يكونوا قادرين على اللحاق بالركب.
Mr. Gu,
السيد غو،
just put me down. Let's rest for a bit.
أنزلني فقط. لنرتاح قليلاً.
You...
أنت...
Your shoulder...
كتفك...
You saw it all.
لقد رأيت كل شيء.
So,
لذا،
you really are
أنت كذلك حقاً
a handful.
حفنة.
I heard something over there!
سمعت شيئاً هناك!
Mind if I deal with those clingy pests first?
هل تمانع إذا تعاملت مع تلك الحشرات المزعجة أولاً؟
I'll leave you somewhere safe.
سأتركك في مكان آمن.
Once I'm done,
بمجرد أن أنتهي،
I'll come back.
سأعود.
Calm down.
اهدأ.
My brother wouldn't be wrong.
لن يكون أخي مخطئاً.
Xie Xinxu is dead.
مات Xie Xinxu.
But if he used certain means to fake his death,
لكن إذا استخدم وسائل معينة لتزييف موته،
and I already saw through him.
وقد كشفت حقيقته بالفعل.
If he comes back.
إذا عاد.
No.
لا.
I have to escape.
يجب أن أهرب.
The rope is too short.
الحبل قصير جداً.
Or should I jump?
أم هل عليّ أن أقفز؟
Too risky.
مخاطرة كبيرة.
If I get hurt,
إذا تعرضت للأذى،
it will draw the Ren.
سيجذب ذلك رين.
I can only try the platform across from here.
لا يمكنني تجربة سوى الرصيف المقابل من هنا.
(Watch on www.kissasia.co, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
(شاهد على www.kissasia.co، .be، .org، .net، .id، .xyz)
Are you mad?
هل انت مجنون؟
I need inhibitors to deal with those Ren.
أحتاج إلى مثبطات للتعامل مع تلك الكلى.
If you stay nearby,
إذا كنت تقيم في مكان قريب،
I'll get distracted.
سأنشغل بشيء آخر.
And besides,
وبالإضافة إلى ذلك،
you hit my shoulder when you opened that cabinet.
لقد ضربت كتفي عندما فتحت تلك الخزانة.
I did not even get angry.
لم أغضب حتى.
You really are
أنت حقاً كذلك
a handful.
حفنة.
So the mark on his shoulder was from that.
إذن، كانت العلامة الموجودة على كتفه نتيجة لذلك.
And he was just complaining that I slowed him down.
وكان يشتكي فقط من أنني أبطأت من سرعته.
We need to get back to the dorm area.
علينا العودة إلى منطقة السكن الجامعي.
If you are going
إذا كنت ذاهباً
to handle something in that room across the way,
للتعامل مع شيء ما في تلك الغرفة المقابلة،
make it quick.
أسرع في ذلك.
So,
لذا،
you were down there the whole time,
كنت هناك طوال الوقت،
quietly watching me
يراقبني بهدوء
climb the rope?
تسلق الحبل؟
You looked so focused,
لقد بدوتَ شديد التركيز،
I did not want to interrupt.
لم أكن أرغب في المقاطعة.
The back is dirtier.
الجزء الخلفي أكثر اتساخاً.
The front is dirtier.
الواجهة الأمامية أكثر اتساخاً.
Do you have to look so disgusted?
هل يجب أن تبدو بهذا القدر من الاشمئزاز؟
In this weather,
في هذا الطقس،
a backless outfit is cold.
الملابس المكشوفة الظهر تجعل الجو بارداً.
You coming or not?
هل ستأتي أم لا؟
Coming.
آت.
They kept rushing us to wait by the nearest elevator,
ظلوا يُسرعون بنا للانتظار عند أقرب مصعد،
and this broken thing still is not fixed.
وهذا الشيء المكسور لم يتم إصلاحه بعد.
Are they expecting us to take the stairs?
هل يتوقعون منا أن نصعد الدرج؟
Leaders are always like this.
القادة دائماً هكذا.
They are not the ones climbing.
إنهم ليسوا من يتسلقون.
Exactly.
بالضبط.
I'll draw them away.
سأشتت انتباههم.
Use the key and get back to the dorm area.
استخدم المفتاح وعد إلى منطقة السكن الجامعي.
I'll shake them off and find you.
سأتخلص منهم وأجدك.
I still have a few inhibitors.
لا يزال لدي بعض المثبطات.
Trust me.
ثق بي.
Who is that, acting so bold?
من هذا الذي يتصرف بهذه الجرأة؟
Stop.
قف.
That is Mr. Gu's inhibitor.
هذا هو مثبط السيد غو.
Then this means...
هذا يعني...
[Morgue]
[المشرحة]
♪I'm begging, begging you…♪
♪أنا أتوسل إليك، أتوسل إليك…♪
Mr. Gu.
السيد غو.
♪I warn you, I warn you♪
♪أحذرك، أحذرك♪
♪So put your loving hand out, darling…♪
♪مدّي يدكِ الحنونة يا عزيزتي…♪
You...
أنت...
You are a Ren.
أنت رين.
Perfect timing.
توقيت مثالي.
I was tired of pretending anyway.
كنت قد سئمت من التظاهر على أي حال.
Long time no see.
وقت طويل لا رؤية.
Xie...
شيه...
Xie Xinxu.
شيه شينكسو.
You...
أنت...
Weren't you dead?
ألم تكن ميتاً؟
He died four years ago, illness.
توفي قبل أربع سنوات بسبب المرض.
♪The touch of your warm embrace♪
♪لمسة حضنك الدافئ♪
♪I'm a slave to you♪
أنا عبدٌ لك
♪Can you feel that you're my fire?♪
♪هل تشعر أنك ناري؟♪
This is
هذا هو
a secret.
سرّ.
Those three Ren kidnapped me before.
هؤلاء الثلاثة من رين اختطفوني من قبل.
Then it was you.
ثم كنت أنت.
Your memory came back?
هل عادت إليك ذاكرتك؟
Blame those idiots.
ألقوا اللوم على هؤلاء الحمقى.
They should not have targeted you.
كان ينبغي ألا يستهدفوك.
I had to step in.
كان عليّ أن أتدخل.
But then
لكن بعد ذلك
your scent made me lose control for a moment.
رائحتك جعلتني أفقد السيطرة للحظة.
I scared you,
أخفتك،
and almost ruined our reunion.
وكاد ذلك أن يفسد لم شملنا.
Luckily,
لحسن الحظ،
you believed the story about the toxic mushroom soup.
لقد صدقت قصة حساء الفطر السام.
That put everything back on track.
هذا أعاد الأمور إلى نصابها.
What do you want?
ماذا تريد؟
To trick me into forming a pact with you?
هل تريد خداعي لأعقد معك اتفاقاً؟
♪You smell like something strange♪
رائحتك غريبة!
♪Like wood♪
♪مثل الخشب♪
♪Like wine♪
♪مثل النبيذ♪
♪Like the fading rain♪
♪مثل المطر المتلاشي♪
♪It's not a problem I can fix♪
♪ليست مشكلة أستطيع حلها♪
♪Maybe I'm just meant to be your toy♪
♪ربما أنا مجرد لعبة بالنسبة لك♪